const questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?",
        answers: ["The Enterprise", "The Millennium Falcon", "The Tardis", "The Death Star"],
        correctAnswer: "The Millennium Falcon",
        category: "Starships",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Chewbacca is from?",
        answers: ["Kashyyyk", "Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor"],
        correctAnswer: "Kashyyyk",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "hard"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the bounty hunter that captures Han Solo?",
        answers: ["Boba Fett", "Jango Fett", "Dengar", "Bossk"],
        correctAnswer: "Boba Fett",
        category: "Characters",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Luke Skywalker is from?",
        answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Tatooine",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Princess Leia is from?",
        answers: ["Alderaan", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Alderaan",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Obi-Wan Kenobi is from?",
        answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Stewjon", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Stewjon",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Anakin Skywalker is from?",
        answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Tatooine",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Yoda is from?",
        answers: ["Dagobah", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Dagobah",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Darth Maul is from?",
        answers: ["Dathomir", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Dathomir",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Darth Vader is from?",
        answers: ["Tatooine", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Tatooine",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Count Dooku is from?",
        answers: ["Serenno", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Serenno",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the planet that Jabba the Hutt is from?",
        answers: ["Nal Hutta", "Hoth", "Endor", "Naboo"],
        correctAnswer: "Nal Hutta",
        category: "Planets",
        difficulty: "easy"
    },

]

module.exports = questions;